[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "You'll to have to ask him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and it just -- I just don't want to say any incriminating things that are going to make it harder to kind of make peace.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$200"]}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "Will you quiet down, you hear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "I want my $200!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Tatum, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "I'm well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, I've always thought you were a part of our family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Do you have an overwhelming sense of relief, both of you, do you think, that at least you've managed to get back to somewhere even if it's not perfect yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "How did you feel when he asked you over for Father's Day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I felt like I would be there for him because it's Father's Day and it's the day our show launches and it seemed like the right thing to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Have you watched it together yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "When you see that little girl in \"Paper Moon\" -- a role that changed your life -- when you see that, do you wish sometimes you'd never been pushed into that world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "``", "NN", "NNP", "''", ":", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "I don't really think about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "CC", "``", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Do you ever -- do you still watch it every now and again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Of course and \"What's Up Doc?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Oh, yes, with my daughter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "About him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Let's focus on you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "About me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["98 percent"]}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "How much have the drugs played a part in the downside of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I would say 98 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "How did you get them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "They were around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "People's houses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "People's houses.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "And what was the drug?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "First pot, then Quaaludes, I think, and then -- first alcohol actually, and then, you know, it just led on and on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "You'll have to ask him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and it just -- I just don't want to say any incriminating things that are going to make it harder to kind of make peace and have a healing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJS", ",", "DT", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What have been your worst moments involving drugs when you look back, the ones where you felt most ashamed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, obviously like you showed, the arrest, that was terrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "How did you get to heroin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Through a friend, a person, after my divorce.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Still call him friend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "'NEAL: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "When you look at yourself now, what do you see and what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "I feel good about myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "I thought, well, this is a very attractive, normal-looking woman, how can this be the crazy Tatum O'Neal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Thank you for saying that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tatum O'Neal"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Do you think you're winning the battle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "I know I'm winning the battle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "How long have you been clean now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I've been sober for a year now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "And are you proud of that, yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Like beyond.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Do you recognize that kind of self-destruct button?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "What's the best way for any addict to try and deal with it once this has all been blown up like it has?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "There are so many different ways now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "What did you find was the best way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "For me, a 12-step program worked for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Did it save your life, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "I know it's saving my life a day at a time, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "How do you physically feel these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ":", "RB", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Do you miss drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Not even -- not even a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Are you surprised at that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "I'm grateful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "And did you feel not a sense of abandonment but something like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I felt the sense of abandonment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Did you ever get mad at her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "And I was sort of like, you know, looking at her pictures and thinking, gosh, you know, how I am going to kind of compete?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "She was one of the most beautiful women in the world, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Did you have any real relationship with her for a long time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Just that one that I write about in my book, where I went to talk to her while she knew she was sick in her apartment, and got to kind of talk to her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Was she sorry to you for what had happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Do you think she was the love of your dad's life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Well, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Well, if you know my dad, and you'll get to meet him, you'll sort of see that he is just always joking and stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Is he basically just an incurable romantic, do you think, your dad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Totally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "He loves women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "You're so right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What was it like walking around with Ryan O'Neal after \"Love Story\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "It was fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan O'Neal"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "What was the most exciting thing you ever did, when you look back at it, wow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "I did some fun things with my ex-husband as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Was he any good, George?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Yes, and nice, gosh, he was so nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Good tennis player?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "He even destroyed George Harrison's game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Well, he was sort of giving a little lesson to Ben, his son, who is now grown.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Harrison"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Who left the biggest impression on you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "So far I honestly would have to say Oprah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "I would have, but I think I was...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1975"]}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "You must be offended, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Listen, when I saw him with the Faces, it was 1975.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Where was he taking you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "He was taking me to the car because I was sleeping because I was 11.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Why do you think that it never really happened in the way it should have done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I'm not really sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "What are you suspicions?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "I wouldn't tell you, because they're my suspicions, so I'm not going to say it on national television.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Would you like to be in a movie again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "'NEAL: I think I would like to be working in a way that was just where I would be considered kind of thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Do you get offers at the moment, or are people still a little wary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Well, for -- I think people are wary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Would you employ yourself right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I would totally employ myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tatum"]}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "When you walk around, what reaction do you get from the public these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Oh, I get a lot of women saying, we love you, Tatum.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Are you on Twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "You're not following me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "Well, I will now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "What's your address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "@Tatum_Oneal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Don Lemon"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "And when come back, I want to ask you on that same theme, really, do you think you're going to live happily ever after now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "I'm Don Lemon live in New York.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Well, do you know how old I was when I married him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Twenty-two.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "CD", "VBN", "NNS", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "How do you get on these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "We get on as well as a divorced couple who have three grown kids can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Do you talk regularly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "Do you talk to your ex-wife regularly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "Every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Six years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Maybe two.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Two years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "Whose decision was it to end the marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Mine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "How did he take that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "Not well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "What's your love life like these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Oh, I don't have any love life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Zero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "Zero.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "Are you looking for a man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "No, I'm really not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "What kind of man do you think now you ought to be with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Maybe a gentle, smart, loving person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "Would you like to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "Wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]